{"data":[{"question":"The use of credit cards in place of cash _________ rapidly in recent years.","a":"have increased","b":"has increased","c":"were increased","d":"have been increasing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" the use of\"- singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Advertisements on television ___ more competitive than ever before.","a":"is become","b":"are becomed","c":"are becoming","d":"is becoming","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" Advertisements\"- plural ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Anything _________ than doing nothing.","a":"is good","b":"are good","c":"are better","d":"is better","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, anything someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There _________ little change in the patient's condition since he was moved to the intensive care unit.","a":"have been","b":"is had","c":"are having","d":"has been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- In sentences beginning with here or there, the subject follows the verb. \n- The subject is \"little change in the patient's condition\" - singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Never before ___ so many people in Taiwan been interested in baseball.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The subject is \" so many people in Taiwan\" which is plural noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He wanted to make his son receive a good education, travel extensively, and ___.","a":"to other advantages are many more","b":"many other advantages","c":"enjoy many other advantages","d":"many other advantages are stored by him","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"travel\" and \"receive\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Robert didn't know whether to sell his books or ___.","a":"to keep them for reference","b":"if he should keep them for reference","c":"keeping them for reference","d":"kept for reference","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \" to sell\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Everybody who ___ a fever must see a doctor immediately.","a":"is","b":"has","c":"are","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"-The pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them\n\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, anything someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Each student ___ the first three questions.","a":"have answered","b":"have been answered","c":"has been answered","d":"has answered","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, anything someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"All work and no play ___ Jack a dull boy.","a":"is made","b":"are made","c":"makes","d":"make","answer":"3","explain":"\n- All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy is a proverb. It means that without time off from work, a person becomes both bored and boring. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}